A Guide to the Papers of The World Affairs Council of Hampton Roads 1968-2000
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
- 1980s
  - Programs and Events
    - WAC Event - Yoshio Hatana, Minister of Economic Affairs, Japanese Embassy May 27, 1981 (Box-folder 8:22)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Ephraim Evron, Ambassador from Israel July 1, 1981 (Box-folder 8:23)
    - The English Speaking Union of The United States Event - Sir Ronald Gardner-Thorpe, Mayor of London September 1, 1981 (Box-folder 8:24)
    - WAC Event - Panel Discussion with John Fahey, Captain Richard Creecy, USN, (Ret.) and Lt. Colonel John Lamond, USA, (Ret.) September 17, 1981 (Box-folder 8:25)
    - WAC Event - Lt. General Necip Torumtay, Director of Operations, Turkish Army October 23, 1981 (Box-folder 8:26)
    - United Nations Association of Virginia - United Nations Day October 24, 1981 (Box-folder 8:27)
    - WAC Discussion Series November 4, 1981 (Box-folder 8:28)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Rafic Jeuejati, Ambassador from the Syrian Arab Republic November 23, 1981 (Box-folder 8:29)
    - WAC Event - Mervat Tallaway, Egytpian Diplomat December 10, 1981 (Box-folder 8:30)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Thomas Mroczkowski, Visiting Polish Professor at ODU January 21, 1982 (Box-folder 8:31)
    - United Nations Association - Annual Dinner January 29, 1982 (Box-folder 8:32)
    - WAC Great Decisions 1982 (Box-folder 8:33)
    - WAC Event - Captain Ulrich Weisser, German National Liaison Representative to Supreme Allied Command Atlantic February 23, 1982 (Box-folder 8:34)
    - WAC Event - Ernestine Heck, U.S. Department of State March 18, 1982 (Box-folder 8:35)
    - WAC Event - Paul Tribble, Representative of the First Congressional District of Virginia April 14, 1982 (Box-folder 8:36)
    - WAC Event - Clovis Maksoud, Ambassador to the United Nations from the Arab League of Nations April 19, 1982 (Box-folder 8:37)
    - WAC Event - Admiral Sir Cameron Rusby, Royal Navy, Deputy Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic May 11, 1982 (Box-folder 8:38)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Russell W. Ramsey, Director Turner Job Corps Center, Management and Training Corporation June 9, 1982 (Box-folder 8:39)
    - WAC Event - Tony Perram, Operations Advisor in the Industry Department of the World Bank June 23, 1982 (Box-folder 8:40)
    - WAC Event - K.R. Narayanan, Ambassador from India September 21, 1982 (Box-folder 8:41)
    - WAC Event – September 22, 1982 - Dr. Betty Diener, Secretary of Commerce and Resources for the Commonwealth of Virginia September 22, 1982 (Box-folder 8:42)
    - WAC and Armed Forces Staff College Event - Ambassador Jerrold M. North, State Department Representative to the Armed Forces Staff College September 30, 1982 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - WAC and Alliance Fraicaise Chapitre de Grasse Event - Ambassador Bernard Vernier-Palliez, Ambassador from France November 2, 1982 (Box-folder 9:2)
    - WAC Event - Captain James R. Bruner, USN, Staff Judge Advocate for the U.S. Atlantic Command November 10, 1982 (Box-folder 9:3)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Francisco Fiallos Navarro, Ambassador from Nicaragua November 23, 1982 (Box 9:4)
    - WAC Event - Admiral Wesley L. McDonald, Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic and Commander in Chief Atlantic Fleet December 14, 1982 (Box-folder 9:5)
    - International Programs at ODU undated (Box-folder 9:6)
    - WAC Event - Lino Gutierrez, U.S. Department of State January 27, 1983 (Box-folder 9:7)
    - WAC Great Decisions 1983 (Box-folder 9:8)
    - WAC and United Nations Association, Peninsula Chapter Event - James Sutterlin, Executive Office, United Nations Secretary General February 22, 1983 (Box-folder 9:9)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Yoshio Okawara, Ambassador from Japan March 8, 1983 (Box-folder 9:10)
    - WAC Event - Grant Mouser, Consul General of the American Consulate in Hamburg, Germany April 14, 1983 (Box-folder 9:11)
    - WAC and English Speaking Union of the U.S., Hampton Roads Branch Event - Kenneth Taylor, Consul General of the Canadian Consulate in New York City April 26, 1983 (Box-folder 9:12)
    - WAC Event - Ron Brinson, President, American Association of Port Authorities May 24, 1983 (Box-folder 9:13)
    - WAC Event - Robert Krulwicke, Chief Business and Economic Correspondent with National Public Radio June 7, 1983 (Box-folder 9:14)
    - WAC Event - G. William Whitehurst, U.S. House of Representatives June 24, 1983 (Box-folder 9:15)
    - WAC English Speaking Union of the U.S., Hampton Roads Branch Event - Bruce T. George, member of the British Parliament September 15, 1983 (Box-folder 9:16)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Jerome Bookin-Weiner, Director, Center for International Programs, ODU September 28, 1983 (Box-folder 9:17)
    - WAC Event - Charita Planas, a leading democratic opponent to the Marcos government October 3, 1983 (Box-folder 9:18)
    - WAC Event - Judge Preston Caperton Shannon, Chairman of the State Corporation Commission October 19, 1983 (Box-folder 9:19)
    - United Nations Association - Annual Dinner October 24, 1983 (Box-folder 9:20)
    - WAC Event - Edmond O.Z. Chipamaunga, Ambassador from Zimbabwe October 27, 1983 (Box-folder 9:21)
    - WAC Event - Edward A. Peniche, International Studies Department, Central Virginia Community College November 23, 1983 (Box-folder 9:22)
    - WAC Event - Richard Parker, Former Ambassador to Lebanon December 1, 1983 (Box-folder 9:23)
    - WAC Event - Kasem Samosorn Kasemari, Ambassador from Thailand December 15, 1983 (Box-folder 9:24)
    - WAC Event - Ernesto Rivas-Gallont, Ambassador from El Salvador January 19, 1984 (Box-folder 9:25)
    - Great Decisions 1984 (Box-folder 9:26)
    - WAC United Nations Association, Peninsula Chapter Event - Doudou Diene, Director of UNESCO, New York Office February 23, 1984 (Box-folder 9:27)
    - WAC Event - Allan Gottlieb, Ambassador from Canada March 22, 1984 (Box-folder 9:28)
    - WAC Event - Byong Hion Lew, Ambassador from South Korea April 12, 1984 (Box-folder 9:29)
    - WAC Event - Lucio Garcia Del Solar, Ambassador from Argentina May 23, 1984 (Box-folder 9:30)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Morris Draper, Armed Forces Staff College May 25, 1984 (Box-folder 9:31)
    - WAC Event - William A. Kirby, U.S. Department of State June 25, 1984 (Box-folder 9:32)
    - WAC Event - Jose Diokno, Former Senator from the Philippines September 13, 1984 (Box-folder 9:33)
    - United Nations Association – October 22, 1984 - Annual Dinner October 22, 1984 (Box-folder 9:34)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Aziz Ali Mohammed, Director, External Relations Department, International Monetary Fund October 25, 1984 (Box-folder 9:35)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Dimitri K. Simes, Senior Associate, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace December 9, 1984 (Box-folder 9:36)
    - WAC Event – January 16, 1985 - Paul Kreisburg, Director for Foreign Relations, WAC New York January 16, 1985 (Box-folder 9:37)
    - Great Decisions 1985 (Box-folder 9:38)
    - WAC Event - A. Hasnan Habib, Ambassador from the Republic of Indonesia February 28, 1985 (Box-folder 9:39)
    - WAC Event - Zeiden Atashi, Member of the Knesset from the Shinui Party, Israel March 13, 1985 (Box-folder 9:40)
    - WAC Event - S.K. Hu, Deputy Representative, Coordination Council for North American Affairs, Taiwan April 25, 1985 (Box-folder 9:41)
    - WAC and United Nations Association, Peninsula Chapter Event - Paul Warnke, Former Arms Negotiator May 14, 1985 (Box-folder 9:42)
    - Armed Forces Staff College Event - Dr. Charles C. Moskso, Jr., Professor of Sociology, Northwestern University May 29, 1985 (Box-folder 9:43)
    - WAC, American Association of University Women, and Women’s Club of Norfolk Event - Major General Kenneth Jolemore, Commandant, Armed Forces Staff College June 4, 1985 (Box-folder 9:44)
    - WAC Event - Ahmed Bourzaim, Deputy Chief of Mission, Embassy of Morocco September 10, 1985 (Box-folder 9:45)
    - WAC and ODU Model United Nations Society Event - G. William Whitehurst, U.S. House of Representatives October 24, 1985 (Box-folder 9:46)
    - WAC Event - Mark G. Eambley (Hambley), U.S. Department of State November 19, 1985 (Box-folder 9:47)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Edward M. Ifft, Senior State Department Representative to Nuclear and Space Talks December 5, 1985 (Box-folder 9:48)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Heinz K. Meier and Louis I. Jaffe, Professor of History, ODU January 28, 1986 (Box-folder 9:49)
    - Great Decisions 1986 (Box-folder 9:50)
    - WAC Event - Dolf Droge, Freelance Lecturer, Writer and Consultant on National and International Issues February 26, 1986 (Box-folder 9:51)
    - WAC and Virginia Center for World Trade Event - Han Xu, Ambassador from the People’s Republic of China March 10, 1986 (Box-folder 9:52)
    - WAC Event - Francis Ghiles, North African Correspondent of the Financial Times of London March 17, 1986 (Box-folder 9:53)
    - WAC Event - Dr. John R. Watt, Director, American Bureau for Medical Advancement in China March 27, 1986 (Box-folder 9:54)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Russell W. Ramsey, Author and Consultant on Central American Affairs April 17, 1986 (Box-folder 9:55)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Don Neuchterlein, Professor of International Affairs at the Federal Executive Institute in Charlottesville April 24, 1986 (Box-folder 9:56)
    - WAC Event - Panel Discussion with John Fahey, Anne Fitzpatrick, Major John Markowicz, and Dr. Patrick Rollins May 20, 1986 (Box-folder 9:57)
    - WAC Event - Lieutenant Colonel Yakup Ozturk and Major Sevino, Turkish Officers at the Armed Forces Staff College June 11, 1986 (Box-folder 9:58)
    - WAC Event - Grant E. Mouser, Former U.S. Department of State Representative at the Armed Forces Staff College September 24, 1986 (Box-folder 9:59)
    - WAC Event - Panel Discussion with Eugene Zajac, Glen Allen Scott, and Dr. William Jones October 29, 1986 (Box-folder 9:60)
    - WAC Event - Admiral Lee Baggett, Jr., Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic and Commander-in-Chief U.S. Atlantic November 25, 1986 (Box-folder 9:61)
    - WAC Event - Admiral Harold E. Shear, U.S. Navy (Ret.), Former Director, U.S. Maritime Administration December 16, 1986 (Box-folder 9:62)
    - WAC Event - Rear Admiral Barry Melbourne Hussey, Naval Attaché for the Argentine Navy in Washington, D.C. January 20, 1987 (Box-folder 9:63)
    - WAC Event - Norman A. Graebner, Professor Emeritus of History and Public Affairs at the University of Virginia February 18, 1987 (Box-folder 9:64)
    - Great Decisions 1987 (Box-folder 9:65)
    - WAC Event - Ambassador Robert E. Fritts, U.S. Diplomat-in-Residence, Department of Government, College of William and Mary March 5, 1987 (Box-folder 9:66)
    - Armed Forces Staff College - Dr. Eugene Rostow, Former Assistant Secretary of State March 10, 1987 (Box-folder 9:67)
    - WAC Event - Sir Antony Acland, Ambassador from Great Britain and Northern Ireland March 19, 1987 (Box-folder 9:68)
    - WAC Event - Kjell Eliaseen, Ambassador from Norway April 23, 1987 (Box-folder 9:69)
    - WAC Event - G. William Whitehurst, Former Congressman, 2nd District of Virginia May 12, 1987 (Box-folder 9:70)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Fredrick F. Chien, Representative of the Coordination Council for North American Affairs for the People’s Republic of China (Taiwan) June 12, 1987 (Box-folder 10:1)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Donald Ainslee Henderson, Dean and Professor of Epidemiology and International Health at John’s Hopkins September 9, 1987 (Box-folder 10:2)
    - WAC Event - Gunter van Well, Ambassador from West Germany October 1, 1987 (Box-folder 10:3)
    - WAC Event - Hermann Dehennin, Ambassador from Belgium October 8, 1987 (Box-folder 10:4)
    - WAC Event - John Craig, Department of State October 26, 1987 (Box-folder 10:5)
    - WAC Event - Sukru Elekdag, Ambassador from the Republic of Turkey November 12, 1987 (Box-folder 10:6)
    - Department of State - 5th Annual Conference with the Former Secretaries of State, Dean Rusk, William Rogers, Henry Kissinger, Cyrus Vance, Edmund Muskie, and Alexander Haig December 18, 1987 (Box-folder 10:7)
    - Assorted Invitations 1987 (Box-folder 10:8)
    - Proposed Topics January through June 1988 (Box-folder 10:9)
    - WAC Event - Vice Admiral Sir Richard Thomas, KCG, OBE, Deputy Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic January 21, 1988 (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Great Decisions 1988 (Box-folder 10:11)
    - WAC Event - Paul Heinbecker, Political Minister, Embassy of Canada February 24, 1988 (Box-folder 10:12)
    - WAC Event - Rear Admiral Ronald J. Kurth, President of Naval War College and Former Senior Military Attaché of the American Embassy in Moscow March 24, 1988 (Box-folder 10:13)
    - WAC Event - Gideon Remez, Chief of Political News Desk, Israel Broadcasting Authority, Israel April 21, 1988 (Box-folder 10:14)
    - WAC Event - Takayuki Kimura, Consul General, Consulate of Japan in Atlanta, Georgia May 26, 1988 (Box-folder 10:15)
    - WAC Event - Dr. MacArthur Corsino - Consul in Embassy of the Republic of the Philippines June 23, 1988 (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Soviets Meet Hampton Roads September 8, 1988 (Box-folder 10:17)
    - WAC Event - Vladimir Pozner, Soviet Commentator October 20, 1988 (Box-folder 10:18)
    - WAC Event - Andreas Kakouris, Consul of the Republic of Cyprus November 10, 1988 (Box-folder 10:19)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Joseph W. McCaffrey, Division Head of the National Oceanic Research and Development Activity, Office of Navy Research December 8, 1988 (Box-folder 10:20)
    - WAC Event Topics 1989 (Box-folder 10:21)
    - WAC Event - Robert Brumley, II, General Consul, U.S. Department of Commerce January 19, 1989 (Box-folder 10:22)
    - Great Decisions 1989 (Box-folder 10:23)
    - WAC Event - Allan C. Brownfeld, Associate Editor of the Lincoln Review March 2, 1989 (Box-folder 10:24)
    - WAC, Alliance Francaise, ODU Women’s Association and Town-N-Gown Event - Dominique Galouzeau de Villepin, Head of Press and Information Services of the French Embassy March 16, 1989 (Box-folder 10:25)
    - WAC Event - Sukru Elekdag, Ambassador from the Republic of Turkey April 12, 1989 (Box-folder 10:26)
    - WAC Event - Ryszard Krystosik, Minister-Counselor, Deputy Chief of Mission, Embassy of Polish People’s Republic May 11, 1989 (Box-folder 10:27)
    - WAC Event - Tong-Jin Park, Ambassador from the Republic of Korea June 1, 1989 (Box-folder 10:28)
    - WAC Event - A Dialogue with Three Czechoslovakian Citizens with Dr. Antonin Mikan, Vendula Nechanicka and Pavel Nechanicky July 27, 1989 (Box-folder 10:29)
    - WAC Event - Joseph Sayah, Political Officer, Embassy of Lebanon September 7, 1989 (Box-folder 10:30)
    - WAC and Forward Hampton Roads Event - Dr. Freidrich Hoess, Ambassador from Austria October 5, 1989 (Box-folder 10:31)
    - WAC, English Speaking Union, and Town –N-Gown Event - Tommy T.B. Koh, Ambassador from the Republic of Singapore November 8, 1989 (Box-folder 10:32)
    - WAC and League of Women Voters Norfolk-Virginia Beach Event - Peter Hakim, Staff Director, Inter-American Dialogue, Aspen Institute, Washington, D.C. November 30, 1989 (Box-folder 10:33)
    - WAC Event - WAC Founder’s Day Reception December 10, 1989 (Box-folder 10:34)
    - Biographies undated (Box-folder 10:35)
  - Budget and Finance
    - Hampton Roads Chamber of Commerce undated (Box-folder 10:36)
    - Scholarship Fund undated (Box-folder 10:37)
    - Tax Exemption undated (Box-folder 10:38)
  - Publicity and Publications
    - Newspaper Clippings 1980-82 (Box-folder 10:39)
    - Publicity Committee / Press Releases undated (Box-folder 10:40)
    - Publications - Printing 1980s (Box-folder 10:41)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1988-89 (Box-folder 11:1)
    - Newspaper Clippings 1989 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Soviet / USA Citizen Diplomacy undated (Box-folder 11:3)
    - World Affairs Councils undated (Box-folder 11:4)
    - Miscellaneous - Notes undated (Box-folder 11:5)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Photos
    - U.S. - Soviet Meeting - Webb Center Photos I undated (Box-folder 11:7)
    - U.S. - Soviet Meeting - Webb Center Photos II undated (Box-folder 11:8)
- 1990s
  - Organization
    - By-Laws 1990s (Box-folder 12:1)
    - Incorporation undated (Box-folder 12:2)
    - WAC Goals and Purpose undated (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Business
    - WAC Report to Numbers undated (Box-folder 12:4)
    - Meeting Announcements undated (Box-folder 12:5)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1990 (Box-folder 12:6)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1991 (Box-folder 12:7)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1992 (Box-folder 12:8)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1993 (Box-folder 12:9)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1994 (Box-folder 12:10)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1995 (Box-folder 12:11)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1996 (Box-folder 12:12)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1997 (Box-folder 13:1)
    - WAC Minutes 1998 (Box-folder 13:2)
    - WAC Minutes and Agendas 1999 (Box-folder 13:3)
    - Advisory Committee 1990s (Box-folder 13:4)
    - Nominating Committee 1990s (Box-folder 13:5)
    - Possible Strategic Alliance with Foreign Policy Association undated (Box-folder 13:6)
    - Report on Visits to California undated (Box-folder 13:7)
    - Strategic Plans 1990s (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Correspondence
    - Correspondence 1990-91 (Box-folder 13:9)
    - Correspondence 1992-93 (Box-folder 13:10)
    - Correspondence 1994-95 (Box-folder 13:11)
    - Correspondence 1996-97 (Box-folder 13:12)
    - Correspondence 1998-99 (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Membership
    - Membership Lists 1992-93 (Box-folder 13:14)
    - Membership Lists 1994-95 (Box-folder 13:15)
    - Membership Lists 1996-97 (Box-folder 13:16)
    - Membership Lists 1998-99 (Box-folder 13:17)
    - Report to Membership 1990 (Box-folder 13:18)
    - Report to Membership 1991-92 (Box-folder 13:19)
    - Report to Membership 1992-93 (Box-folder 13:20)
    - Report to Membership 1993-94 (Box-folder 13:21)
    - Report to Membership 1994-95 1994-95 (Box-folder 14:1)
    - Report to Membership 1995-96 1995-96 (Box-folder 14:2)
    - Report to Membership 1996-97 (Box-folder 14:3)
    - Report to Membership 1997-98 (Box-folder 14:4)
    - Report to Membership 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14:5)
    - Membership Dues 1990s (Box-folder 14:6)
    - Board Memberships 1990s (Box-folder 14:7)
    - Corporate Members undated (Box-folder 14:8)
    - Special Memberships 1990s (Box-folder 14:9)
    - Membership Brochures and Pamphlets undated (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Programs and Events
    - Program Committee undated (Box-folder 14:11)
    - Program Speakers File undated (Box-folder 14:12)
    - Programs 1990s (Box-folder 14:13)
    - Azalea Festival - Ingvi S. Ingvarsson, Ambassador of the Republic of Iceland April 16, 1990 (Box-folder 14:14)
    - Azalea Festival - Juan Cassiers, Ambassador from Belgium April 16, 1991 (Box-folder 14:15)
    - Azalea Festival - Jaime de Ojeda, Ambassador from Spain April 21, 1992 (Box-folder 14:16)
    - Azalea Festival - Vice Admiral Peter W. Cairns, CMM, CD, CAN Commander Maritime Command April 20, 1993 (Box-folder 14:17)
    - Azalea Festival - Francisco Jose Treichler Knopfli, Ambassador From Portugal April 19, 1994 (Box-folder 14:18)
    - Azalea Festival - Phillip Thomas, Senior Counsellor for Politico- Militart Affairs, British Embassy April 24, 1995 (Box-folder 14:19)
    - Azalea Festival - Adriaan Jacobovitis de Szeged, Ambassador from The Kingdom of the Netherlands April 16, 1996 (Box-folder 14:20)
    - Azalea Festival - Jeremy D. Rosner, Special Advisor to the President and Secretary of State April 23, 1997 (Box-folder 14:21)
    - Azalea Festival - K. Erik Tygesen, Ambassador from the Kingdom of Denmark April 22, 1998 (Box-folder 14:22)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series Sponsors undated (Box-folder 14:23)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Maja Wessels, "Commercial Banks and International Competitiveness" April 11, 1991 (Box-folder 14:24)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Charles E. (Chip) Roh, Jr., "The U.S. - Mexico Free-Trade Pact" June 28, 1991 (Box-folder 14:25)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - " Lord Francis Arthur Cockfield, “Update: European Affairs" October 22, 1991 (Box-folder 14:26)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Benjamin N. Brown, "How to Do Business With Eastern Europe" March 20, 1992 (Box-folder 14:27)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - William T. Archey, "Changing Trends in World Trade – Are We Ready?" March 31, 1993 (Box-folder 14:28)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Francine Lamoriello, "European Community Update" June 23, 1993 (Box-folder 14:29)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Mark Borthwick, "Trade Opportunities with the Pacific Rim" December 10, 1993 (Box-folder 14:30)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - M.L. Birabhongse, "Doing Business with Thailand" January 14, 1994 (Box-folder 14:31)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Julius L. Katz, "U.S. and Foreign Trade - What’s Happening? What will happen?" March 15, 1994 (Box-folder 14:32)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Nguyen Dang Thuyen, "Vietnam Today" June 20, 1994 (Box-folder 14:33)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Stephen J. Solarz, "New World Order or Disorder: Contemporary Challenges to American Foreign Policy?" December 6, 1994 (Box-folder 14:34)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Susan B. Levine, "Development Banks: Opportunities for U.S. Banks" March 28, 1995 (Box-folder 14:35)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Timothy J. Hauser, "Global Opportunities in the Big Emerging Markets" May 12, 1995 (Box-folder 14:36)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Dana Du Rand, "Post Apartheid South Africa and the US: A New Era in Business and Politics" November 17, 1995 (Box-folder 14:37)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - C. Thomas Burke, "Panama Canal and the Year 2000" February 23, 1996 (Box-folder 14:38)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Franklin C. Phifer, Jr., "Developments in Trade Legislation" June 7, 1996 (Box-folder 14:39)
    - Corporate Luncheon Series - Frank Capiello, "The New American Economy: The View From Wall Street" July 2, 1996 (Box-folder 14:40)
    - Great Decisions Committee undated (Box-folder 14:41)
    - Great Decisions 1990 (Box-folder 14:42)
    - Great Decisions 1991 (Box-folder 14:43)
    - Great Decisions 1992 (Box-folder 14:44)
    - Great Decisions 1993 (Box-folder 14:45)
    - Great Decisions 1994 (Box-folder 14:46)
    - Great Decisions 1995 (Box-folder 14:47)
    - Great Decisions 1996 (Box-folder 14:48)
    - WAC Event - Nayan Chanda, Senior Associate, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace and Bureau Chief for the Far Eastern Economic Review January 18, 1990 (Box-folder 15:1)
    - WAC and KPMG Peat Warwick Event - Francine Lamoriello, Manager of International Department, KPMG Peat Warwick February 15, 1990 (Box-folder 15:2)
    - WAC and Town-N-Gown Event - Karl Th. Paschke, Minister Plenipotentiary of the Federal Republic of Germany March 8, 1990 (Box-folder 15:3)
    - WAC Event - Dr. Edward J. Lincoln, Brookings Institute May 10, 1990 (Box-folder 15:4)
    - WAC Event - Rita Klimova, Ambassador from Czechoslovakia June 7, 1990 (Box-folder 15:5)
    - WAC and Foodbank of Southeastern Virginia Event - Dr. William Hawley, Medical Director, U.S. Public Health Service June 21, 1990 (Box-folder 15:6)
    - WAC Event - Vice Admiral Sir James Weatherall, KBE, Deputy Supreme Allied Commander, Atlantic September 12, 1990 (Box-folder 15:7)
    - WAC and ODU Event - Thomas R. Pickering, Ambassador from the U.S. to the United Nations (cancelled) October 25, 1990 (Box-folder 15:8)
    - WAC and EVMS Event - Dr. Carl E. Taylor, Consulate to the Government of China November 8, 1990 (Box-folder 15:9)
    - WAC Event - Michael J. Cook, Ambassador from Austrailia December 6, 1990 (Box-folder 15:10)
    - WAC Event - Richard C. Holbrooke, Managing Director, Lehman Brothers January 23, 1991 (Box-folder 15:11)